{
    "id": "7342028731d94b3f8caacf9a3a4e0631",
    "title": "Intermediate Level Grammar Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "I think we should buy ……………………… car.",
            "description": "Another means besides this / an alternative.",
            "answers": [
                "other",
                "an other",
                "another"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "You never think of …………………………..",
            "description": "Others can mean the other people.",
            "answers": [
                "other",
                "another",
                "others"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "………………………… they refuse to admit it, their marriage is on the verge of collapse.",
            "description": "We use although to connect two contrasting ideas. It is a conjunction and connects clauses.",
            "answers": [
                "Although",
                "Despite",
                "However"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "Stop fooling …………………………. We are already late.",
            "description": "To fool around/about is to indulge in silly or time-wasting activities.",
            "answers": [
                "about",
                "around",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "I will love her as long as I ………………………….",
            "description": "After as long as we use a present tense to refer to the future.",
            "answers": [
                "live",
                "will live"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "We are painting the house ………………………… Easter.",
            "description": "We use at to talk about the whole of holidays.",
            "answers": [
                "on",
                "at",
                "with"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "If we want to get there by evening, we ………………………….. hurry.",
            "description": "Had better is used to give strong advice.",
            "answers": [
                "have better",
                "better",
                "had better"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "She was brought ………………………… by her maternal grandmother.",
            "description": "To bring up a child is to raise her.",
            "answers": [
                "off",
                "up",
                "on"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "There is something ………………………. the bed.",
            "description": "Under and underneath can both refer to physical position.",
            "answers": [
                "under",
                "underneath",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "You cannot but ……………………… her courage.",
            "description": "We use the infinitive without to after cannot but.",
            "answers": [
                "admire",
                "admiring",
                "to admire"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "How ………………………… money do you earn in a month?",
            "description": "We use much before uncountable nouns.",
            "answers": [
                "much",
                "many"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "How …………………….. sisters do you have?",
            "description": "We use many before plural nouns.",
            "answers": [
                "many",
                "much"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        }
    ]
}